

About Me

Front End Developer with Two years of experience in Responsive pixel perfect web design and Web application. My greatest strength is quick learner, Hard worker, Willing to learn new technology.

Contact

+91 9943567950







www.linkedin.com/in/anthony-m1995/ 363, South street, Elaynkanni,

Thandrampet, Tiruvannamalai

manthonysuresh@gmail.com

Education

606753

2013 - 2017

Completed B.E Mechanical Eng., in Mahendra Engineering College, Namakkal with CGPA 8.23

2011 - 2012

Completed HSC in Carmel Hrs. Sec. School, Elayankanni with 79.8%

2009 - 2010

Completed SSLC in Carmel Hrs. Sec. School, Elayankanni with 74%

Anthony M Front End Developer



https://anthonym995.github.io/portfolio/

Experience

FRONT END DEVELPOER - AUG 2021 - MAR 2022

Billionapps Infotech Solutions/Chennai - Developing pixel perfect responsive web design & web application, Adobe Marketo, Converting Adobe XD, Figma design to web application, Wordpress basics.

FRONT END DEVELOPER - JULY 2020 - JULY 2021

Itechuniversal/Chennai - Developing pixel perfect responsive web design and web application, Bootstrap, ¡Query, Git, Adobe Xd.

Professional Skills



Additional Skills

| Angular Material | Git | AJAX | JSON |
|------------------|--------|-------|-----------|
| Less/Scss | jQuery | uı/ux | MS Excell |

Hobbies

Playing Chess Rubik's Cube Mobile Games **Listening Songs**

Personal details

28/05/1995 Marital Status: Unmarried Date of Birth :

Father's Name: Magimainathan Mother's Name: Francismary

: Tamil, English, Hindi Languages